Okay, everyone, I'm
literally on Monday, and it's Saturday in two days, approximately.
I'm gonna be going on my first ever backpacking trip, so let's get ready for the backpacking trip.
Let's pack, let's get food, and then we're gonna go on the trip, and you're gonna come along with me.
So I just thought it'd be fun to take you guys through the whole process as I do it for the very first time in my life ever.
So yeah, okay, to go on my first backpacking trip ever, the first thing that I need is a backpack.
So I am going to get a backpack.
I have an idea of the one that I want to get.
So what I need to do is I need to get a backpack, I need to get food, and then I pretty much have everything
else, like I have all the clothes and actually a decent amount of the camping gear.
So pretty much just a backpack and food.
So let's head out on a journey to find that.
Okay, I have my list of things to gather, so let's go.
First to the store to get food, or should I get other things first?
Yes, guys, I'm literally so excited to go and get some
snacks and backpack and things I need.
Just kidding.
I actually got my backpack a couple days ago.
Right now, I'm going to the grocery store.
On my list, I have some carrots, some apples.
I just want to get things that aren't going to bruise or go bad doing it overnight.
So lots of like snacks like that.
So I'm going to go to the grocery store and get those.
I also have to get some wet wipes for my armpits, my face, and all that stuff, so I don't become gross and smelly.
And I also have to get mini deodorant.
I already have a mini toothpaste, so that's good, but yeah, that's uh, it's pretty
much what I need today.
Okay, we've arrived.
Let's go into the grocery store and get some groceries.
There
are
a couple more things that I got.
I got this canned coffee.
I've had it before.
It's like, it's okay, so it's just nice to have a coffee in the morning.
I got jerky, so got some beef jerky.
Will be a good snack, some protein.
So the next thing I got is this meal.
Apparently you actually don't even need a bowl, which is so fabulous, but the flavor that I got was yellow curry with chicken and rice because it's gluten
free, and the reviews are very positive.
This has very good reviews, so it must be good.
So I'm excited to try this out.
I've never had a camp, a dehydrated meal before, so or freeze dried meal before.
So we see how that goes.
I also got these water treatment tablets so I don't get a disease.
But it turns out my friend already got some, so I didn't really need to get them.
I also have and gonna bring these granola bars, which actually Go Macro sent them to me.
So thanks, guys.
And I've tried them a couple times, they're pretty good.
And they also don't have any gluten in them.
And it's all kind of natural protein sources, which is good because whey protein actually really bugs my stomach.
Then I also got bear spray.
And then I also got a water bottle that you just scoop up.
Scoop up the water from the river, and you can drink it because it has a, it has a filter.
So we'll see how that goes, but this is everything I bought.
And one more thing, one more purchase is this bad boy.
Yes!
Now I have, I officially have a backpacking backpack.
Yay!
This is awesome.
This is the Osprey Atomos bag.
It's the 65 liter one.
I got the bigger one because I'm going to use it when I travel.
I need it to go down a little bit.
So I'm going to use it when I travel, and then also for like backpacking, and I also want to do more backpacking trips, so I was
like, I'm just gonna get the bigger one.
So here we go.
It feels very secure.
So we got all the food and stuff ready, and I'm gonna start packing my bag.
Okay, some other things we got all my water bottles, bear spray, my toiletries, and like toothbrush and everything, a pillow, my sleep mat, and
oh, yeah, sunglasses, too.
This is the bag with all the food in it.
I still have more food that I have to add.
I also have a sleeping bag, but I'm pretty much all packed up.
Oh my god, my backpack is genuinely so full, but I have finished packing for for.
The trip.
Yes, everything's ready to go.
Yes, so ready.
It was August 27th, and we had just set out on our grand adventure.
So we were driving up to Whistler for the evening, just to stay overnight, so we didn't have to get up super super early the next day.
The drive was about an hour and a half, but we did stop in Squamish for some food and whatnot, and then we also went to the village
to gather some supplies for dinner, which we decided to make burgers.
I got these gluten-free buns that actually tasted like play-doh, but the rest of the burgers were good, and once we had dinner, we just kind of hung
out for a bit and then went to bed.
Time to go to bed; it's the night before for the hike.
See you tomorrow.
July 28th, got up bright and early at 6:30 in the morning, made myself a coffee, and then crafted two beautiful sandwiches to accompany me for my
hike, for my lunch.
Then I made a protein smoothie and had some toast among other things, and then got dressed to go on the hike.
Outfit is on.
So we left it around 8, and then ended up getting there around 9 to begin the hike.
Get him.
I'm definitely gonna get it like out of here.
Yeah.
Can you give us a spin, please?
Oh yeah.
And so the hike began.
I actually did this hike last year with my dad.
I don't know if you guys saw that video, but this time was a little bit different as we were camping overnight.
It has commenced.
For some reason, going into this hike, I was so convinced I would be completely fine, and that the extra 30 pounds on my
back, 30 to 40 pounds on my back, would not be much of an issue.
And boy, was I wrong.
Luckily, our campground was about 8 kilometers into the hike.
Unfortunately, though, it was 8 kilometers of straight uphill and 900 meters of elevation.
It's currently 9:43.
We've done 2.38 kilometers.
Despite the difficulty, we persevered nonetheless, taking quite a few breaks along the way, and eventually we got up to the
campground around 11:30.
Currently at the campsite, trying to find a place to lay down our stuff.
So let's get going.
Let's go!
It's beautiful.
Should I keep going?
Keep rolling.
Keep on rolling, boy.
Yay, our home for the night.
Once we arrived at the campsite, we just kind of set everything up because we didn't really want to do it when we got back.
So we set up our tent.
We actually put the pegs in the wrong way the first time.
But anyway, we set up our tent, sleeping bag, all that kind of stuff, and then we had some lunch.
I had two sandwiches for lunch as I was very hungry, and then we kind of got ready to go for the next leg of our trip.
We started the next leg of the hike at around one o'clock, and it was about five and a half kilometers to get up to Panorama
Ridge, and the hike up there was genuinely so beautiful.
All the wildflowers were out, and it's just kind of otherworldly up there.
Alright,
there's where we're headed.
Go right ahead.
Perfect.
Alright, so this is where we're gonna go hike up there.
We are currently up in the meadow.
We have how many kilometers left?
Like three?
I think about two and a half, three kilometers.
You don't see that every day.
You really don't.
I don't think I ever get over how beautiful this hike is.
It's my favorite hike that I've ever done.
It's just so beautiful and calming and peaceful up here, and the views are completely just unmatched, and I just feel so peaceful up in the mountains.
Anyway, at this point, we are about one kilometer from the top, which is a pretty brutal, completely uphill scramble, but it is so worth it for the
views you get to see.
So
we stayed up at the top for about an hour, just
trying to take in all of the natural beauty that we had just witnessed, and then at around four, we decided to climb back down.
On our way back down, we collectively decided that we wanted to do a quick detour to Garibaldi Lake, which is the nearby lake that you actually saw
when we were up on Panorama Ridge.
That's Garibaldi Lake.
And we were all feeling very sweaty and dusty and wanted To take a swim before heading back to the campsite.
And dive.
Oh, God.
I feel awesome.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh god, I gotta get out of here!
Is it that cold?
Yeah, it's really cold.
Is it nice though?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, it definitely goes in.
But I'm really convinced I'm here.
Yes, I'm taking a video.
We headed back to the campsite, and by the time we got back, it was time for dinner.
So we just had dinner, and now we're hanging out in Ruby's tent.
We're hanging out and laughing.
Let me organize it, and then we can do it.
Okay, then we'll do a tent tour.
Good morning.
Woke up around 6:30.
It was actually completely freezing when we woke up, which was crazy.
I was not expecting that.
But anyway, had some breakfast, had some coffee, some oats, peanut butter, an apple, very tasty breakfast, and then
had to warm up in the tent for a little bit before deciding to pack up and head back down.
My toes are literally so cold.
It's okay.
I'm just sitting and warming up, and then we're going to get ready and hike back down in a bit and go home.
So, yeah.
Gotta start disassembling everything.
Then, this marked the end of our trip.
We hiked back down.
It was about two and a half hours to get back down.
The entire hike down, I was just feeling so happy and grateful for the experience, my lovely friends, and everything we got to see and do.
And I'm so excited to do more overnights in the future.
On the drive back down, we stopped for a post-hike obligatory burger, and then after that, just went home.
I finally arrived home.
The first shower is gonna hit, and then I'm gonna have a nap.